## MALESELA SETWABA

JUNIOR FULL STACK DEVELOPER & BUSINESS ANALYST



### **PERSONAL**

**Phone**: 081 866 7435

**Email**: setwabat3@gmail.com

Physical & Postal Address: 44 Panorama Avenue, Kempton Park, Gauteng, 1619

**ID**: 9512235319089

**Drivers License**: Code 10

**Gender**: Male

DOB: 23 December 1995

Nationality: South Africa

Languages:
English (Fluent), Sepedi (Home)

#### **SKILLS & TECH STACK**

• HTML, CSS, SCSS, JS

REACT, ANGULAR, VUE, LARAVEL

Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap 5

 Database Design (MySQL, MongoDB, Firebase)

• Business Analysis

Problem-Solving

Computer Literacy

Project Management Tools

Strong Communication

## **EDUCATION**

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER AND INFORMATION SCIENCES

IIEMSA 2020 - 2023

Accredited by the CHE. Registration: NQF Level 7, SAQA ID 88605

## **ABOUT ME**

Bachelors in Computer and Information Sciences graduate majoring in Business Analysis. I have volunteer experience in business analysis coupled with experience in developing full stack web applications and I have a passion for coding and business, so I enjoy blending the two worlds together to solve real-world IT problems.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **VOLUNTEER FRONTEND DEVELOPER & BUSINESS ANALYST**

**TNG SOLUTIONS -** 19 Richards drive, Gallagher Convention Centre March 2022 - November 2022

- Assisted coding team on front-end development of a property management application and video-conferencing application.
- Responsible for preparing BPMN, UML and use case diagrams to model the applications functions and behavior.

#### **VOLUNTEER BUSINESS ANALYST**

MOTOTRACE AUTO SPARES - 36 ERNEST OPPENHIEMER AVE, BRUMA January 2023 - Current

- Responsible for implementation of inventory and sales management system using ZOHO.
- Assisted in sales and procurement.

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

ECBA (ENTRY CERTIFICATE IN BUSINESS ANALYSIS) International Institute of Business Analysis (IIBA) September 2023

ECBA certification imparts essential skills in requirements analysis, stakeholder engagement, process modeling, and problem-solving. It equips professionals with the expertise to bridge the gap between business needs and IT solutions, facilitating informed decision-making and project success.

## **REFERENCES**

#### **Alvin Matewa**

CEO, TNG Solutions

Phone: 066 264 2512

Email: alvin@tngsolutions.co.za

#### **Lord Setwaba**

CEO, Mototrace Auto Spares

Phone: 082 523 4707

Email: parts@mototrace.co.za



# **International Institute of Business Analysis**

certifies that

Malesela Setwaba

has successfully completed the

**Entry Certificate in Business Analysis™** 







Issued: September 20, 2023

Certificate: 82459423